VLAD KOSMACH

SOFTWARE ENGINEER



ABOUT ME

Over 5 Years of IT Experience. Extensive SOLID. Excellent communication, presentation and interpersonal skills. Middleware Application server design and development, Multithreaded applications. Object-Oriented analysis, design, development and implementation. Excellent communications skills, creative problem solver, proactive listener, and the ability to work in a team or individually and easy adaptation with changing technology are my professional

CONTACT ME

Phone

+38(073) 42-17-457

Address

Vinnytsia, Ukraine

Emai

ivlad003@gmail.com

Website

WORK EXPERIENCE

2018 - Present THE GLYPH STUDIO

Software Engineer JS

Angular, SCSS, CSS, HTML, JS, NODEJS, MongoDB, Java

apel8.com eprs.com intouch.me

autumncompass.com

2017 - 2018 GOGO CAB

Mobile Software Engineer

Support for old functionality and adding new features

2015 - 2017 LINDENVALLEY GMBH

Middle Android Developer

Creating applications from 0 to release. Support for old applications. Created by project architecture.

2014 - 2015 FREELANCE

Mobile Developer

Created two applications related to construction using opengl.

2013 - 2014 TECHFUNDER

Android Developer

Project: Metrotile. Used languages: Java, SQL, XML. The project was created in Eclipse IDA. Also participated in the design of the

database.

EDUCATION

2012 - 2014 IT Step Academy/University

Software Engineer

PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

PERSONAL SKILLS

Java

JavaScript

Communication ___

Teamwork

Stress

Management

Mentoring

HTML CSS

Angular